<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Cairo TourGuide</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="Museum">Museum</string>
    <string name="top5">TOP 5</string>
    <string name="cafe">Cafe</string>
    <string name="Malls">Malls</string>
    <string name="parks">PARKS</string>
    <string name="mu_info1">The Museum of Egyptian Antiquities is one of the must-see attractions on any itinerary to Cairo. The museum holds the most extensive collection of Egyptian antiquities in the world. The museum is housed in the first purpose-built museum building in the world on Tahrir Square. The neoclassical building was designed by Marcel Dourgnon and has 107 halls with artifacts spanning from the prehistoric period through the Roman era. The majority of exhibits are focused on the pharaonic era with 160,000 artifacts covering 5,000 years of Egyptian history.</string>
    <string name="mu_info2">The Coptic Museum was initially inaugurated in 1910 and most of the collection comes from donations and contributions. It holds the world’s largest collection of Egyptian Christian items. “Coptic” means Egyptian Christian Church; the Coptic Period in Egypt was during the 3rd-7th century bridging the gap between Roman religion and the Muslim conquest in the 7th century. As the Copts were present during the late Roman and Byzantine Egyptian eras their art displays elements of Greco-Roman, Byzantine and even Muslim culture.  In 1939 the Egyptian Service of Antiquities moved their collection of Christians Antiquities from the Egyptian Museum to the Coptic Museum. Ever since that time all artifacts found at Christian sites or related to Christian history in Egypt are displayed here. The museum manages to link the Coptic history in Egypt with the Pharaonic, Greco-Roman and Islamic antiquities and show how the different cultures influenced Coptic art. The museum is housed within the walls of the Fortress of Babylon in Coptic Cairo. Also within the walls are Cairo’s historic churches including St. Sergius; the 4th century St. Barbara and the Hanging Church dating back to the 6th century. The museum covers 8,000m² and includes various Christian buildings and gardens.</string>
    <string name="mu_info3">This museum is housed in two 16th century Ottoman-era houses which have been restored and furnished in various Oriental styles. Each room in the connecting 5 floor houses has a theme of a particular oriental style including Egyptian, Moroccan and Japanese, Persian, Byzantine, Mohammed Ali era, Damascus and contains artifacts and antiques. Former resident of the houses, Major Gayer-Anderson, an English doctor in the Egyptian civil service in the 1930s and 1940s donated his home and collection which he amassed during his travels. The houses hold pieces from various historic periods including the Pharaonic and Islamic as well as Central Asian art, objects from Iran and Turkey and paintings by 20th century artists. The collection includes birthing chairs and ethnomedical equipment which interested Gayer-Anderson as a medical professional. You can also see miniature Persian paintings, Persian cupboards from a Teheran palace, Chinese paintings on rice paper, engraved ostrich eggs, a mummy case, a Turkish Harem toy, a recreated Turkish apartment, carpets and other curiosities, antiques and memorabilia.</string>
    <string name="mu_info4">This museum (MIA) has a collection of over 103,000 artifacts which was amassed starting in 1880 on the orders of Khedive Ismail Pasha who asked that archaeological rarities from the Islamic era be gathered and preserved. The art is displayed in collections according to the historic era. The museum came to its present building in 1903 and has continued to expand its collection through purchases, donations and excavations. The scope of the collection also expanded to include pieces from throughout the Islamic world and from the 7th century to the end of the 19th century. The pieces are displayed in 25 halls and an archaeological garden. The work is displayed in chronological order from the Umayyad, Mamluk, Ottoman eras to groups of work from the same country like Turkey and Persia. There are also themed sections according to the type of art like funeral art, epigraphy, calligraphy, glassware, metalwork and astronomy.</string>
    <string name="mu_info5">The Abdeen Palace in Cairo was built under Khedive Ismail to replace the Citadel as the official government headquarters. It was designed by French architect Rosseau and was completed in 1874. Until the abolition of the monarchy the palace was used as a royal residence; from 1872 to 1952 it functioned as the seat of government until the coup d’etat which overthrew King Farouk. Today the upper floors are reserved for use as offices and the official residence of the President of Egypt. the palace witnessed many historic events over the years and is often mentioned in history books. The palace was built on the site of a small mansion which had belonged to Abidin Bey (c.1780-1827) an Albanian commander and politician in Egypt during the Muhammad Ali era.</string>
    <string name="TOP_INFO1">The Giza Pyramids stand 13km from Cairo’s city center, visible from many parts of the city. Three pyramids, the Great Sphinx, minor tombs, a workers’ village and several ancient cemeteries make up the archaeological site on the Giza plateau. They are one of the Seven Wonders of the World, a UNESCO site and the one attraction you should see if you have time for nothing else while in Cairo. The pyramids were built as burial tombs for three generations – the grandfather, Khufu was buried in the Great Pyramid; his son, Khafre is buried in the second pyramid and his son Menkaure was buried in the smallest of the pyramids.</string>
    <string name="TOP_INFO2">Locals and tourists alike come to the Cairo Tower to take in the breathtaking views across the city of a thousand minarets. The free-standing tower is located on Gezira Island (Zemalak) not far from the Museum of Modern Art. The body of the tower is made of granite and has intricate latticework which slightly fans out at the top of the tower like a lotus flower. The tower was designed by Naoum Shebib and constructed from 1954 to 1961. Egyptian president at the time Gamal Adbel Nasser claimed that the US government had gifted him $6,000, 000 to win his favor and to rebut their attempt to bribe him he would use the money to build the tower.</string>
    <string name="TOP_INFO3">The ancient Egyptian pharaohs were buried in pyramid shaped tombs the most famous being at Giza on the edge of the Cairo’s city center, but in Dahshur there is another location where you can see pyramids. Dahshur is located about 40km south of Cairo and its pyramids are among the oldest, best preserved and largest Egyptian pyramids. Dahshur sees fewer tourists than Giza and its pyramids are perhaps less photogenic. It is believed that the pyramids of Dahshur were constructed under Snofu , the first ruler of the 4th dynasty and father of Khufu who built the Great Pyramid of Giza. The pyramids of Dahshur show a stage in the development of the Egyptian pyramid building techniques between the step sided to smooth sided pyramid styles.</string>
    <string name="TOP_INFO4">This ancient Nilometer or al-Miqyas was used to measure the level of the Nile River. The Nile flooded in the summer months of July to November and when the waters receded in September-October a layer of rich silt deposits would be left on the river banks creating fertile farming land. The Egyptians have been dependent on this flooding since ancient times and they devised a way to help them predict the ebb and flow of the floods. The flooding was vital for agriculture and meant the difference between prosperity and starvation. The ancient Egyptians devised a way of measuring the Nile’s annual floods in order to predict the future harvests. For 5,000 years the Egyptians recorded the Nile’s water levels.</string>
    <string name="TOP_INFO5">Although there are several markets (souk) in Cairo Khan el-Khalili is the largest and most exciting. The souk attracts tourists as well as locals coming to do their regular shopping. This is the place where you will really see a slice of genuine Cairo life and get some amazing photos. The site where Khan el-Khalili now stands was originally part of the Fatimid Great Eastern Palace complex which was begun in the first century. By the 14th century, during the reign of Mamluk Sultan Barquq his Master of Stables destroyed the Fatimid mausoleum and cemetery to create a large khan or caravanserai – a place for merchants and their wares. The khan was at the heart of the commercial city and great buildings like the Al-Azhar Mosque and al-Hussein Mosque were built nearby. The area around the khan became a center for foreign trade including slave trading. The last Mamluk Sultan al-Ghuri made changes to the layout of the souk in the 16th century adding monumental gates and streets which crossed the main street of the souk; each street specialized in a particular trade. As you walk through the labyrinth of lanes today you can still see elements of the original architecture like the gates and vaulted ceilings.</string>
    <string name="mall_INFO1">Spanning a land area of over 3 million sq. m (700 acres), Cairo Festival City is a visionary mixed-use urban community strategically located at the gateway to New Cairo city. Cairo Festival City sets new standards as Egypt’s premier indoor-outdoor shopping, dining and entertainment destination, providing spectacular residential villas and luxurious apartments, as well as prime office spaces, together with internationally renowned hotels, international schools and automotive showrooms all set within a beautifully landscaped and tranquil community.A state-of-the-art, centralized customer contact centre, run by City Management will offer residents and guests a 24/7 service to ensure that Cairo Festival City is maintained and operated at the highest standard.Combining a relaxing lifestyle and picturesque landscapes, the many parks, gardens, walkways and plazas bring together the districts to enhance and foster gatherings for family and friends as an addition to Cairo Festival City amenities. A truly distinctive lifestyle experience where meticulous attention to detail is obvious and all elements of the project are seamlessly interconnected.</string>
    <string name="mall_INFO2">Stars Centre is the retail and leisure component of the Citystars Heliopolis complex and provides a unique shopping and entertainment experience to the Middle East.With the best local retailers combined for the first time with international brand names, shopping has not only become a pleasure but an entirely new experience. In fact, more than just shopping, Stars Centre offers a combination of entertainment and dining facilities that are unmatched anywhere else in Cairo some of which are Mosaique dining zone and the Family Restaurant Area. In addition to the unrivaled 21-screen cinema complex, Stars Centre also contains Golden Stars Cinema. These cinemas feature recliner seating in a refined interior design while serving delicious meals and refreshments during the movie display by Holiday Inn Cairo Citystars in addition to our VIP restaurants Mori Sushi and Tamara. The premises contain two indoor theme parks; E-Zone and Magic Galaxy, which cover a combined area of almost 9000 sqm.</string>
    <string name="mall_INFO3">Al Arabi Development Center in the Kingdom of Saudi Arabia on 6th of October in the field of Wagineh on 24 December 2010 and owned by the Egyptian Center for Real Estate Development.
The mall includes a number of shops, telecommunications companies, cinemas, sports venues, banks, a dancing fountain, a large restaurant hall and many other areas, both international and local, with a large garage that can accommodate many cars.</string>
    <string name="mall_INFO4">Mall of Egypt is the first shopping destination of its kind in Egypt. The mall is owned and managed by Majid Al Futtaim, the leading pioneer in shopping malls, retail, and leisure across the Middle East and North Africa region.Mall of Egypt is located on Al Wahat Road in 6th of October City.With a Gross Leasable Area (GLA) of 165,000 square meters, Mall of Egypt houses the best local and international retailers, including an unparalleled high-end fashion offering of the world’s most prestigious brands. Moreover, the mall will house major department stores as well as other fashion, lifestyle, sports, electronics, fine dining, and home furnishing outlets.With direct access to Wahat Road, the mall includes 6,500 car parking spaces.Mall of Egypt’s family leisure services include Ski Egypt – Africa’s first indoor skiing slope, a 21 multi-screen VOX Cinemas, and a Magic Planet family entertainment centre.</string>
    <string name="mall_INFO5">Founded in 1997, by Mr. Mohamed Genena under the umbrella of M.G. Group .Genena mall is the leading shopping mall and entertainment pioneer in Egypt.Genena Mall has improved the shopping habits of millions of people across the country. We had the vision of changing the culture of street shopping in respect of presenting a full shopping experience in just one place to make shopping easier.It is continuously a successful business story, Genena Mall started from a simple idea and turned to be a huge business where everyone is participating to serve with a high level of Excellency and help people to fulfill all their needs and enjoy their time with the first ice skating in Egypt.By gathering a valuable mix of international and local brands, including Daly Dress, LC Waikiki, Accessorize, Charles and Keith, Magrabi, Nike, Adidas, Daniel Hechter and many more With a total shopping area 22000 square for more than 300 shop we can simply saying it’s the best shopping mall with affordable prices.</string>
    <string name="park_INFO1">This garden was created along the lines of the French Garden - Jardin de Clachemione.The park is the first of its kind in the Middle East and is located on an area of 70 acres and is fully managed through modern electronic systems.
It includes a cultural and entertainment complex and miniature models of (Bibliotheca Alexandrina, Giza Zoo and the Military Museum) as well as green areas on 35 acres.
To provide entertainment for the family that can spend the whole day enjoying the greenery and the exercise of children to the games, which gain new educational information, skills and abilities that allow their vital interaction with the existing tools and technologies that unleash their thinking. The garden is designed to provide an entertaining educational experience for children and their families through programs And events that stimulate knowledge, creativity and lifelong learning.
The park also combines tourism and culture together through (theater, museum, music and arts) and sports and recreational activities (adventures, magic river, open fields).</string>
    <string name="park_INFO2">Located in Zamalek in Jabalia Street in Cairo, it was established by Khedive Ismail in 1867 and is considered one of the best gardens established in the era of Khedive in Cairo. The garden is managed by the zoo in Giza in 1902. It has repaired 24 ponds to display 33 A type of Nile fish in it before the opening of the park to the public officially on 21 November 1902.
The park was closed in 1965 for a long time. It was repaired and renovated and supervised by the scientific and engineering authorities of the Egyptian Ministry of Agriculture. It was opened again in 1983.
It has an area of more than nine acres and a half acres.</string>
    <string name="park_INFO3">Al Azhar Park is one of the largest parks in Greater Cairo and one of the largest and most beautiful gardens in the world. It has been used on an area of ​​80 acres in the past as a landfill for more than a thousand years. The project was announced in 1984 and opened to visitors in 2005, where construction took more than 7 years, at a total cost of more than 100 million Egyptian pounds, paid by the Aga Khan Foundation for Islamic Architecture.
Located on the west side of the old Fatimid city park and its extension is the Red Route, with a wealth of mosques and shrines, and a long line of minarets. To the south is Sultan Hassan Mosque and the surrounding areas. In addition to Saladin Castle, this area was already in need of an open green area. The garden  offers high views of the city and offers 360-degree panoramic views of historic Cairo.</string>
    <string name="cafe_INFO1">In these difficult days of Egypt’s dwindling tourism, we thought it might be the perfect time to revisit El Fishawy, the legendary Cairo cafe where famed Egyptian novelist Naguib Mahfouz  reportedly penned parts of his Nobel Prize winning novels.
There are no long waiting lines to get a table. and gone too are the crowds that could intimidate those with mild claustrophobia.
Some of our Egyptian friends staunchly refuse to frequent this cafe, condemning it for having become too touristy and overrated. While it is indeed true that the legendary coffeehouse is more likely to be filled with tourists and unappreciative patrons these days  as opposed to the intellectuals and writers of Mahfouz’s lifetime . it still offers an unforgettable atmosphere of Old Cairo.</string>
    <string name="cafe_INFO2">Cilantro is an Egypt-based Western style coffee shop, offering gourmet coffee, a variety of beverages and a selection of fresh sandwiches, salads, pastries, desserts, and snacks.
In 2000, Cilantro introduced the concept of “Chain Coffee Shops” to the Egyptian market with its first branch located in the heart of Zamalek; a branch that started the evolution of the coffee shop scene in Egypt and continued to the new modernized coffee shop approach and thereby paving the way for many national and international chains to penetrate the market.
Today, Cilantro has over 60 branches across Egypt, serving 3 million visitors per year; striving to cater to different demographics through its different brands and formats in streets, malls, gas stations, educational facilities, corporate and office buildings.</string>
    <string name="cafe_INFO3">To say Starbucks purchases and roasts high-quality whole bean coffees is very true. That’s the essence of what we do – but it hardly tells the whole story.
Every day, we go to work hoping to do two things: share great coffee with our friends and help make the world a little better. It was true when the first Starbucks opened in 1971, and it’s just as true today.
Back then, the company was a single store in Seattle’s historic Pike Place Market. From just a narrow storefront, Starbucks offered some of the world’s finest fresh-roasted whole bean coffees. The name, inspired by Moby Dick, evoked the romance of the high seas and the seafaring tradition of the early coffee traders.
In 1981, Howard Schultz (Starbucks chairman and chief executive officer) had first walked into a Starbucks store. From his first cup of Sumatra, Howard was drawn into Starbucks and joined a year later.
In 1983, Howard traveled to Italy and became captivated with Italian coffee bars and the romance of the coffee experience. He had a vision to bring the Italian coffeehouse tradition back to the United States. A place for conversation and a sense of community. A third place between work and home. He left Starbucks for a short period of time to start his own Il Giornale coffeehouses and returned in August 1987 to purchase Starbucks with the help of local investors.
From the beginning, Starbucks set out to be a different kind of company. One that not only celebrated coffee and the rich tradition, but that also brought a feeling of connection.</string>
    <string name="cafe_INFO4">Since 2001, we’ve been brewing our way across Egypt delivering the best in coffee, food and community. Having introduced the contemporary coffee bar culture to Egypt, our strategic growth and defined objectives have secured our position as one of the key coffee brands in the market. With 23 branches throughout Cairo and Alexandria and an impressive schedule for further expansion, Beano’s Cafe is the place to be! Step inside any one of our locations and you’ll see what we mean. Our cozy and inviting interiors are made for all good things—good coffee, good food and good company.</string>
    <string name="cafe_INFO5">to help our customers make the right choice for them we publish nutritional information (including calories) on shelf and on counter for food products and provide a countertop summary card with the calorie information of its most popular drinks.</string>
    <string name="mu_name1">Egyptian Museum</string>
    <string name="mu_name2">Coptic Museum</string>
    <string name="mu_name3">Gayer-Anderson Museum</string>
    <string name="mu_name4">Museum of Islamic Arts</string>
    <string name="mu_name5">Abdeen Palace</string>
    <string name="mu_name3withoutspace">Gayer-Anderson Museum</string>
    <string name="mu_name4withoutspace">Museum of Islamic Arts</string>
    <string name="loc_mu1">Egypt Museum Cairo</string>
    <string name="phone_mu1">0225794596</string>
    <string name="phone_mu2">0223628766</string>
    <string name="phone_mu3">0223647822</string>
    <string name="phone_mu4">0223901520</string>
    <string name="phone_mu5">0223916909</string>
    <string name="top5_name1">The Giza Pyramids</string>
    <string name="top5_name2">Cairo Tower</string>
    <string name="top5_name3">Dahshur Pyramids</string>
    <string name="top5_name4">Nilometer</string>
    <string name="top5_name5">Khan el-Khalili</string>
    <string name="loc_top51">Giza Pyramids</string>
    <string name="loc_top53">Pyramids at Dahshur</string>
    <string name="phonetop52">0227365112</string>
    <string name="phone_top5empity"></string>
    <string name="mall_name1">Cairo Festival City Mall</string>
    <string name="mall_name2">City Stars Mall</string>
    <string name="mall_name3">Mall of Arabia</string>
    <string name="mall_name4">Mall Of Egypt</string>
    <string name="mall_name5">Genena Mall</string>
    <string name="phone_mall_1">16761</string>
    <string name="phone_mall_2">16478</string>
    <string name="phone_mall_3">0238260200</string>
    <string name="phone_mall_4">01024444482</string>
    <string name="phone_mall_5">0220820621</string>
    <string name="cafe_name1">El Fishawi Cafe</string>
    <string name="cafe_name2">Cilantro Cafe</string>
    <string name="cafe_name3">Starbucks cafe</string>
    <string name="cafe_name4">"Beano's Cafe"</string>
    <string name="cafe_name5">Costa cafe</string>
    <string name="phone_cafe_1">0225906755</string>
    <string name="phone_cafe_2">16313</string>
    <string name="phone_cafe_3">0224803740</string>
    <string name="phone_cafe_4">0223585336</string>
    <string name="phone_cafe_5">16460</string>
    <string name="park_name1">Family Park</string>
    <string name="park_name2">Gabalaya Park And\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020Aquarium</string>
    <string name="park_name3">Al Azhar Park</string>
    <string name="phone_park_1">"01159661880"</string>
    <string name="phone_park_2">01091593825</string>
    <string name="phone_park_3">0225103868</string>
    <string name="put_extra_1">name</string>
    <string name="put_extra_2">info</string>
    <string name="put_extra_3">image</string>
    <string name="put_extra_4">location</string>
    <string name="put_extra_5">number</string>
    <string name="location">"geo:0,0?q="</string>
    <string name="number">"tel:"</string>
    <string name="package_map">"com.google.android.apps.maps"</string>
    <string name="location_layout">LOCATION</string>
    <string name="call_layout">CALL</string>
    <string name="over_view">Over View :</string>

</resources>
